A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Press Office Records, 2004-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- III. Multimedia Files, 2004-2010., Extent: 1.44 cubic feet (5 boxes). (Box 9-13)
  - DVDs
    - Attorney General Christmas Party 2007 by David Clementson - 8:43 minutes [abusive driver fees/Santa lost his license plate - includes Robert McDonnell, Marla Decker, Martin Kent, Gov. Tim Kaine] (Box 9, Disc 50)
    - Virginia Forever. Our Land. Our Water. Our Quality of Life. ca. 2007? (Box 9, Disc 51)
    - Virginia State Parks with Governor Tim Kaine, two 30 second PSAs, 9 January 2008 (Box 9, Disc 52)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, State of the Commonwealth Address, 10 January 2008 - 43:21 minutes (Box 9, Disc 53)
    - Governor Tim Kaine press conference at 2008 Biotech Annual Convention, San Diego, California, 18 June 2008 - 12:31 minutes (Box 9, Disc 54)
    - Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Address to Electoral College, December 2008 - 8:00 minutes (2 copies) (Box 9, Disc 55)
    - Consider This, WVPT, Governor Tim Kaine, 26 February 2009 - 26:46 minutes (Box 9, Disc 56)
    - Meet the Farmer TV, No. 25, Specialty Foods and Education Conference, 12 May 2009 - 29:00 minutes (Box 9, Disc 57)
    - NewsPlus with Mark Segraves, DC50 TV, 2 January 2010 episode, includes segment on Governor Tim Kaine - 21:12 minutes (Box 9, Disc 58)
    - Public Service Announcement by Governor Tim Kaine for VINE (Victim Information and Notification Everyday), undated - 0:33 seconds (Box 9, Disc 59)
  - Audio
    - Governor-Elect Tim Kaine Transportation Meeting, Roanoke, Virginia, 18 November 2005, 2 files - 45:44 and 29:14 minutes (Box 9, Disc 60)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Speech to the General Assembly, 16 January 2006 - 42 minutes (1 audio master and 2 service copies) (Box 9, Disc 61)
    - Radio ad by Americans for Prosperity-Virginia in opposition to tax increases proposed by Governor Tim Kaine and State Senate leaders, 20 March 2006 - 1:00 minute (Box 9, Disc 62)
    - Governor Tim Kaine clip from Sandy Lesberg's World, WRRW 100.9 Williamsburg Public Radio, 15 September 2007 - 16 minutes (Box 9, Disc 63)
    - Governor Tim Kaine interviewed on Epicentro Politico, a Spanish language radio program, 5 April 2008 - 59:01 minutes [Kaine interview 18:15-24:40] (Box 9, Disc 65)
    - Ask the Governor, WTOP, 22 December 2009 - 40:57 minutes (Box 9, Disc 66)
  - Digital Photographs on CD
    - Photographs of Governor Mark Warner, Whitewater Rafting, Richmond, Virginia, 27 August 2004 [jpg files] (2 CDs) (Box 10, Disc 1)
    - Portrait of Governor-Elect Tim Kaine, 19 December 2005 [jpg files] (2 CDs) (Box 10, Disc 2)
    - Portrait of First Lady Anne Holton, 3 January 2006 [jpg files] (2 CDs) (Box 10, Disc 3)
    - Governor-Elect Tim Kaine Appoints Secretary of Education Dr. Thomas R. Morris, Arthur Ash Elementary School, 6 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 4)
    - 1 CD containing multiple events [jpg files]: (Box 10, Disc 5)
      - Governor-Elect Tim Kaine at the Dedication of the Springfield Ramp, 10 January 2006
      - Governor Kaine at the January CTB Meeting in Richmond, 18 January 2006
      - Governor Kaine at the VDOT Garver Leadership Conference in Roanoke, 5 April 2006
    - Governor Tim Kaine's Inauguration, Williamsburg, Virginia, 14 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 6)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Virginia Association of School Superintendents (VASS), Library of Virginia, 17 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 7)
    - Virginia Cabinet Members Portraits, 17-24 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 8)
    - Press Availability with Attorney General Robert McDonnell and Transportation News Conference, 20 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 9)
    - Swearing in of Secretary of the Commonwealth Daniel G. Leblanc, 22 January 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 10)
    - David Smith, Steve Mondule, Vivek Kundra, 9 March 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 11)
    - CD Mideast Trip - March 2006, Two Discs (multiple events - jpg files): (Box 10, Disc 12)
      - Afghan Ambassador's Residence, 15 March 2006
      - Afghan Embassy Compound, 15 March 2006
      - Al Saleem Arrival, 13 March 2006
      - Al Saleem Breakfast, 15 March 2006
      - Amb Korologos Breakfast, 17 March 2006
      - Bagram AFB, 16 March 2006
      - Camp Arifjan Dinner, 13 March 2006
      - Camp Eggars, 15 March 2006
      - Camp Eggars Troop Breakfast, 16 March 2006
      - Flight to Baghdad - Overflight photos, 14 March 2006
      - Flight to Iraq, 14 March 2006
      - Flight to Islamabad, 15 March 2006
      - Flight to Kabul, 15 March 2006
      - General Eikenberry, 16 March 2006
      - Green Zone, 14 March 2006
      - Green Zone Memorials, 14 March 2006
      - Helo Photos Kuwait, 13 March 2006
      - Kabul Motorcade, 16 March 2006
      - Sather AB - Baghdad IA - Iraqi Forces Demo, 14 March 2006
      - USAID School, 16 March 2006
    - Governor Tim Kaine's Transportation Town Hall Meeting, Bristol Public Library and Announcement of Kate Hanley as Secretary of the Commonwealth, both 20 March 2006 [jpgs files] (2 cds) (Box 10, Disc 13)
    - Governor Tim Kaine's Staff, Secretaries and Deputy Secretaries, 16 April 2006 (Box 10, Disc 14)
    - Governor Kaine at Ford plant in Norfolk, Virginia, 17 April 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 15)
    - State Employee Governor's Awards, 4 May 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 16)
    - Governor Tim Kaine with Virginia Minority Supplier Development Council (VMSDC) participants at Virginia Business Opportunity Fair (VBOF), 7 May 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 17)
    - Group photograph of Governor Tim Kaine and Cabinet, [Jamestown?], 23 May 2006 [jpg file] (Box 10, Disc 18)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Visit to Queens Park, 29 May 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 19)
    - Governor Tim Kaine at Pocahontas State Park, 17 June 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 20)
    - Bill Signing Ceremony. Governor Kaine will sign legislation that establishes Virginia's goal of attracting highly qualified teachers, and requiring regular, written performance evaluations of public school teachers, 23 June 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 21)
    - Caritas Ribbon Cutting, 29 June 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 22)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Common Health Walk, 24 July 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 23)
    - Roberto Flores Bermudez, Ambassador of Honduras to the United States, 8 August 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 24)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Dismal Swamp Canal Trail, 9 August 2006 (2 copies) [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 25)
    - Sallie Mae "Teach and Care" News Announcement, 15 August 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 26)
    - Governor Tim Kaine Visits the VDOT Salem District and Tours the STC Facility and the New STC Location Underconstruction, 12 September 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 27)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, Northrup Gruman Gift to University of Virginia at Wise, 18 September 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 28)
    - Governor's Mansion Reception, 20 September 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 29)
    - Commonwealth Scholars Reception at the VDOT Auditorium, 28 September 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 30)
    - Governor Tim Kaine's European Trade Mission, 11-18 November 2006 (photographs from 14, 16-17 November) [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 31)
    - 2006 Governor's Housing Conference, Award Luncheon, 30 November 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 32)
    - West Virginia-Virginia Governor's Meeting, Bluefield, West Virginia, 30 November 2006, taken by Steven Rotsch, Governor's Photograph for West Virginia Governor Joe Manchin, III [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 33)
    - Governor's Mansion Reception, 4 December 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 34)
    - Governor's Mansion Reception, 15 December 2006 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 35)
    - Elementary School Principals with Governor Tim Kaine, 29 January 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 36)
    - Virginia Transit Association 2007 Transportation Choices Legislative Reception, 29 January 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 37)
    - Sorensen Institute 2007 Gala Honoring Governor Linwood Holton, 27 March 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 38)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 1 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 39)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 2 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 40)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 3 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 41)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 4 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 42)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 5 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 43)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 6 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 44)
    - Virginia's Royal Welcome, 3 May 2007, State Capitol, CD 7 of 7 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 45)
    - Jamestown 2007, America's 400th Anniversary, Day 1, 11 May 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 46)
    - Jamestown 2007, America's 400th Anniversary, Day 2, 12 May 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 47)
    - Jamestown 2007, America's 400th Anniversary, Day 3, 13 May 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 48)
    - Shubert Family, Colonial Forge Bands, Reception for Senator Chichester and Delegate Callahan, 21 May 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 49)
    - Virginia Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries 3rd Law Enforcement Academy Training, Run with the Governor, 4 June 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 50)
    - Anne Holton Portraits, 6 June 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 51)
    - Governor Tim Kaine, 2007 Girls State, Longwood University, 19 June 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 52)
    - Springfield Interchange Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, photos by Tom Saunders, VDOT, 18 July 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 53)
    - Springfield Interchange Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 18 July 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 54)
    - Oliver Hill Sr., Governor's Mansion, 11 August 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 55)
    - Oliver Hill, Sr., Memorial Service, 12 August 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 56)
    - Security Conference at Virginia Commonwealth University, 15 August 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 57)
    - Reception at Governor's Mansion, 16 August 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 58)
    - APM Terminals Virginia Grand Opening, Portsmouth, 7 September 2007 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 59)
    - A Collection of Photographs: The First Two Years, January 2006-November 2007 (2 copies) (Box 10, Disc 60)
    - Reception at Governor's Mansion, 21 February 2008 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 61)
    - Governor Tim Kaine at WBCH, 16 June 2009 (disc one) [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 62)
    - Governor Tim Kaine at WBCH, 16 June 2009 (disc two) [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 63)
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc one of three) (Box 10, Disc 64)
      - SGA Golf Tournament, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
      - SGA Press Conference, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
      - SGA Reception, Governor's Palace, Williamsburg, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc two of three) (Box 10, Disc 65)
      - SGA Reception, Governor's Palace, Williamsburg, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc three of three) (Box 10, Disc 66)
      - SGA Session 3 and 4, 23 August 2009 [jpg files]
      - SGA First Lady, Cooking Demo, 23 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc one of five) (Box 10, Disc 67)
      - First Lady Anne Holton Luncheon, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
      - SGA Sessions 1 and 2, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc two of five) (Box 10, Disc 68)
      - SGA Sessions 1 and 2, 22 August 2009 [jpg files]
      - Kingsmill, Williamsburg, Virginia, 23-24 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc three of five) (Box 10, Disc 69)
      - Kingsmill, Williamsburg, Virginia, 23-24 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc four of five) (Box 10, Disc 70)
      - Kingsmill, Williamsburg, Virginia, 23-24 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Southern Governors' Association, Annual Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21-24 August 2009 (disc five of five) (Box 10, Disc 71)
      - Kingsmill, Williamsburg, Virginia, 23-24 August 2009 [jpg files]
    - Route 3 Ground Breaking with Governor Tim Kaine, photos by Trevor Wrayton, VDOT, 28 October 2009 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 72)
    - Governor Tim Kaine visits Norfolk Ship Repair, 18 November 2009 [jpg files] (Box 10, Disc 73)
  - Documents on CD
    - Governor's Biennial Executive Budget, 2006-2008 and Amendments to the 2005 Appropriation Act, prepared by Virginia Department of Planning and Budget, December 2005 (pdf files) (Box 11, Disc 1)
    - Shell PowerPoint Presentation, February 2006? (Box 11, Disc 2)
    - 1 CD containing two PowerPoint presentations: (Box 11, Disc 3)
      - Governor Tim Kaine's Transportation Town Hall Meeting, Bristol Public Library, 20 March 2006
      - Governor Tim Kaine's Transportation Town Hall Meeting, Grover King VFW Post 1115, Hillville, 21 March 2006
    - 1 CD containing two PowerPoint presentations: (Box 11, Disc 4)
      - Governor Tim Kaine's Transportation Town Hall Meeting, Sterling, 28 March 2006
      - Governor Tim Kaine's Transportation Town Hall Meeting, Chesapeake Conference Center, 29 March 2006
    - Governor's Workforce Strategic Plan, 16 January 2007 (pdf files) (Box 11, Disc 5)
    - Transportation Accountability Commission, Overview of Current Transportation Accountability and Performance Methods, Commission Briefing, Ralph M. Davis, Deputy Secretary of Transportation, 31 January 2007 (PowerPoint) (Box 11, Disc 6)
    - 2008-2010 Executive Biennial Budget, prepared by Virginia Department of Planning and Budget, December 2007 (pdf files) (2 copies) (Box 11, Disc 7)
    - Executive Amendments to the 2008-2010 Biennial Budget prepared by Virginia Department of Planning and Budget, December 2008 (pdf files) (2 copies) (Box 11, Disc 8)
  - Video Tapes: VHS
    - Consider This with Richard Parker, Guest: Lt. Governor Tim Kaine, 23 January 2004 - 26:46 minutes (Box 11)
    - Consider This with Richard Parker, Guest: Lt. Governor Tim Kaine, ca. February 2004? - 24:10 minutes (Box 11)
    - Consider This with Richard Parker, Guest: Governor Tim Kaine, 14 February 2006 - 26:45 minutes (Box 11)
    - Comcast Metro Richmond - Public Affairs, Read Across America, Governor Tim Kaine PSA, 10 March 2006 - 30 seconds (Box 11)
    - Fatal Contact: Bird Flu in America, ABC TV Network (fiction), 9 May 2006 - 2 hours (Box 11)
    - Nightline, Bird Flu, Governor Tim Kaine interviewed, 9 May 2006 - 30:00 minutes (Box 12)
    - House of Delegates, 13 February 2008, partial recording; Senate of Virginia, 19 April 2006, partial recording (Box 12)
  - Video Tapes: Beta
    - Nightline, Bird Flu, Governor Tim Kaine interviewed, 9 May 2006 - 30:00 minutes (Box 12)
    - Democratic Response to the State of the Union Address, Governor Tim Kaine, 31 January 2006 (Box 12)
  - Photographic Prints
    - Photographic Prints, undated (Box 13)